// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Choose the correct alternative to complete the following sentence: ___________________________________________________________________________  Perfect! I am looking forward to the book fair, too. To my best knowledge it is going to be held in my hometown. It has already been announced for 20/7/2012. So, I hope to see you on _____________. ",
    answer: "the twentieth of July, two thousand and twelve",
    options: [
      " twenty of July, two thousand twelve",
      "the twentieth of July, two thousand and twelve",
      " twenty July, two thousand and twelve",
      "the twentieth July, two thousand and twelve"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Read the following sentences carefully: ___________________________________________________________________________ 1. Do you have a fever, or any other symptoms? 2. I’d like to make an appointment to see the doctor. 3. Dr. Peterson’s office. How may I help you? Yes, I’m not feeling very well. Yes, I have a slight fever and aches and pains.  Certainly, are you ill at the moment?___________________________________________________________________________ The correct order of sentences to form a dialogue is:",
    answer: " 3 2 6 4 1 5",
    options: [
      "3 2 6 5 1 4",
      " 3 2 6 4 1 5",
      "3 4 6 5 2 1",
      "1 2 6 4 5 3"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "ONLY ONE of the words can be used to complete the sentence. ___________________________________________________________________________ Which one? You can only have your money back if you can produce _________.",
    answer: "a receipt",
    options: [
      " a bill",
      "a receipt",
      "a ticket",
      "an invoice"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which question or response fits the situation?: ___________________________________________________________________________ Joe: Would you like to come to my party?Sue: Is your brother going too?Joe: _________________",
    answer: "I’m thinking of it.",
    options: [
      "i I don’t think so",
      "Do you think so?",
      "Yes, we are?",
      "I’m thinking of it."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Your guest is wearing a heavy coat. You say: ‘May I hang up your coat?’ because _______.",
    answer: "you want to make her feel comfortable",
    options: [
      "  you like her coat very much",
      "you want to hang up her coat",
      "you want to make her feel comfortable",
      " you don’t like her coat at all"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Where did you find this book? Don’t you know that __________?",
    answer: " it’s theirs",
    options: [
      " it’s theirs",
      " it’s their",
      "it’s of them.",
      "it’s they’re"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The mugger is someone who __________.",
    answer: "robs people in the street",
    options: [
      "robs banks",
      "breaks into houses",
      "picks pockets",
      "robs people in the street"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Choose the sentence which is in the present perfect tense:",
    answer: "She has just eaten her dinner.",
    options: [
      "They had already left the school.",
      "She will have finished her task.",
      "They would have called the boys.",
      "She has just eaten her dinner."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The sentence ‘They were reading at that time.’ is in_______.",
    answer: "Past continuous tense",
    options: [
      "Present perfect tense",
      "Present continuous tense",
      "Past perfect tense",
      "Past continuous tense"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Look at the following nouns. One of them does NOT exist. Which one?",
    answer: "laboury",
    options: [
       "recovery.",
       "laboury",
       "discovery",
      "slavery"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Choose the best way to join the following sentences:  ___________________________________________________________________________ My friend’s brother was underage.He did not get the job.",
    answer: "My friend’s brother did not get the job since he was underage.",
    options: [
      "My friend’s brother did not get the job since he was underage.",
      "My friend’s brother did not get the job and he was underage.",
      "My friend’s brother did not get the job though he was underage.",
      "My friend’s brother did not get the job so he was underage."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Choose the correct sentence:",
    answer: "Modern factories have fewer workers than in the past.",
    options: [
      "Modern factories have fewer than in the past workers.",
      "Fewer modern factories have workers than in the past.",
      "Modern factories have fewer workers than in the past.",
      "Fewer factories have modern workers than in the past."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "ONLY ONE of the following is a complete sentence. Which one?",
    answer: "We saw the snow falling.",
    options: [
      "I outside this morning.",
      "We saw the snow falling.",
      "Timmy his watch.",
      "Susie’s furry yellow cat."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which word is different?",
    answer: "conference room",
    options: [
      "participants",
      "guest-speakers",
      "organizers",
      "conference room"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Choose ONE word to complete the TWO sentences given below:  ___________________________________________________________________________ I am in a great hurry. Can you, please, give me a _________.Didn’t you know that the __________ is out of order?",
    answer: "lift",
    options: [
      "lift",
      "elevator",
      "ride",
      "drive"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "In the string of words: broke, given, sang, came, spoke, the word given is different because ___________.",
    answer: "it is past participle",
    options: [
      "it is a verb",
      "it is infinitive",
      "it is past simple",
      "it is past participle"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Which notice says, ‘You should put things in the right place.’?",
    answer: "Do not leave bags in front of the room.",
    options: [
      "No entrance to art room – use the other door.",
      "Turn off electronic devices during lessons.",
      "Please return all the books to correct shelves.",
      "Do not leave bags in front of the room."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "This is a sport many of us only see at Olympic Games times, but there is a lot more to it than that. It is a popular activity for many youngsters. At the competitive level, there are the major divisions of this sport to rhythmic and artistic. The sport is called______.",
    answer: "gymnastics",
    options: [
      "dancing",
      "skating",
      "skiing",
      "gymnastics"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "David lives in a spacious house with his parents. Below is the house plan. Apart from the living room, the dining room and the kitchen, there are two bedrooms. One is his parents’ and the other is his own bedroom. His parents’ bedroom is 3.60 X 3.60, whereas David’s bedroom is 3.00 X 2.70 metres.Look at the house plan and choose the correct alternative:",
    answer: "David’s bedroom is smaller for 4.86m2.",
    options: [
      "David’s bedroom is smaller for 4.86m2.",
      "David’s bedroom is smaller for 3.86 m2.",
      "David’s bedroom is smaller for 5.86 m2.",
      "David’s bedroom is smaller for 2.86 m2."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Choose the most suitable alternative to complete this sentence:  ___________________________________________________________________________ If I were you __________.",
    answer: "I wouldn’t fight back",
    options: [
      "I won’t fight back",
      "I wouldn’t fight back",
      "I wouldn’t have fought back",
      "I wouldn’t had fought back"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "Jenna gave a birthday party last night. We all had great fun although we knew it was not her birthday because she was born on 13/06/1992. Jenna was born on_____.",
    answer: "the thirteenth of June, nineteen ninety-two",
    options: [
      "the thirteenth of June, nineteen ninety-two",
      "thirteen of the June, nineteen ninety-two",
      "thirteenth of June, nineteen ninety-two",
      "June thirteenth, of nineteen ninety-two"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "Ben: This is an Identikit picture of Brian Smith. Look for him at airports and seaports.Diana: What has he done? Why is he wanted?Ben: He’s a pickpocket, _____________",
    answer: "he steals money, credit cards, passports…",
    options: [
      "he robs banks and cash-points.",
      "he steals money, credit cards, passports…",
      "he breaks into houses.",
      "he kidnaps children."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 23,
    question: "He always wants to give __________ to people around him.",
    answer: "advices",
    options: [
      "advise",
      "advice",
      "advises",
      "advices"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 24,
    question: "Choose the correct sentence:",
    answer: "We never thought of him as part of the family despite the fact that he was one of us.",
    options: [
      "We thought of him never as part of the family despite that the fact he was one of us.",
      "We never thought of him as part of the family despite the fact that he was one of us.",
      "We never thought of him as of the family part despite that the fact he was one of us.",
      "Despite we never thought of him as part of the family the fact that he was one of us."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "Which word is different?",
    answer: "scorer",
    options: [
      "goal",
      "stadium",
      "ball",
      "scorer"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 26,
    question: "Dianna went shopping yesterday. She first went into a greengrocer’s. She bought a kilo of English apples. They cost £1.85. Then she took a kilo of French pears. They were £1.25. She also bought a kilo of English strawberries and half a kilo of Italian grapes. She paid £2.70 for these. She paid __________ altogether.",
    answer: "five pounds and eighty pence",
    options: [
      "five pounds and eighty pence",
      "six pounds and eighty pence",
      "four pounds and eighty pence",
      "three pounds and eighty pence"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 27,
    question: "Our generation reunion party was held on 28/4/2007. It was held on ______.",
    answer: "the twenty-eighth of April, two thousand and seven",
    options: [
      "April twenty-eighth, of two thousand and seven",
      "twenty-eighth of April, two thousand and seven",
      "twenty-eight of the April, two thousand and seven",
      "the twenty-eighth of April, two thousand and seven"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 28,
    question: "Pierre, Johanna, Patrick, and Rebecca are e-mail friends. They communicate daily because they have many things in common. Look at the table below and choose the correct answer:",
    answer: "Patrick likes going to movies, the others don’t.",
    options: [
      "Patrick likes going to movies, the others don’t.",
      "Johanna likes cooking but Rebecca doesn’t.",
      "Both Pierre and Johanna are employed.k",
      "They all like reading and writing books."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 29,
    question: "Bleron: I didn’t expect to find you home. What are you going to do tonight?Arta: I don’t know yet. ____________.Bleron: To tea?",
    answer: "One of my neighbours has invited me…",
    options: [
      "One of my neighbours has pleased me…",
      "One of my neighbours has welcomed me…",
      "One of my neighbours has invited me…",
      "One of my neighbours has suggested me…"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 30,
    question: "The sentence ‘We have never been so happy in our lives.’ is in the ______.",
    answer: "Present perfect tense",
    options: [
      "Present simple tense",
      "Present continuous tense",
      "Present perfect continuous tense",
      "Present perfect tense"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 31,
    question: "Didn’t you know that _________ cannot be bought in the library?",
    answer: "some books",
      options: [
      "some books",
      "books",
      "the books",
      "those books"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 32,
    question: "Look at the following nouns. One of them does not exist. Which one?",
    answer: "recoverment",
    options: [
      "punishment",
      "parliament",
      "agreement",
      "recoverment"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 33,
    question: "Choose the correct sentence:",
    answer: "Although I don’t believe in miracles, his recovery seems to confront the medical explanations.",
    options: [
      "I don’t although in miracles believe, his recovery seems to defy the medical explanations.",
      "Although I don’t believe in miracles, his recovery seems to confront the medical explanations.",
      "I don’t believe in miracles although, his recovery to defy seems the medical explanations.",
      "I don’t in miracles believe, his recovery although seems to defy the medical explanations."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 34,
    question: "Which word is different?",
    answer: "hotel",
    options: [
      "clinic",
      "hotel",
      "hospital",
      "sanatorium"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 35,
    question: "Which word below does NOT rhyme with the word straight?",
    answer: "night",
    options: [
      "night",
      "great",
      "eight",
      "late"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 36,
    question: "In the string of words: water, milk, packet, petrol, money, the word packet is different because ___________.",
    answer: "it is a countable noun",
    options: [
      "it consists of six letters",
      "it consists of five sounds",
      "it is an uncountable nun",
      "it is a countable noun"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 37,
    question: "Choose the correct sentence:",
    answer: "Although I don’t believe in miracles, his recovery seems to confront the medical explanations.",
    options: [
      "I don’t although in miracles believe, his recovery seems to defy the medical explanations.",
      "Although I don’t believe in miracles, his recovery seems to confront the medical explanations.",
      "I don’t believe in miracles although, his recovery to defy seems the medical explanations.",
      "I don’t in miracles believe, his recovery although seems to defy the medical explanations."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 38,
    question: "Look at the following nouns. One of them does not exist. Which one?",
    answer: "recoverment",
    options: [
      "punishment",
      "parliament",
      "agreement",
      "recoverment"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 39,
    question: "Choose the correct sentence:",
    answer: "I Have not told him the whole story yet.",
    options: [
      "I Have not told him the whole story yet.",
      "I have him not told the whole story yet.",
      "I have not told the whole story him yet.",
      "I not have told him the whole story yet."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 40,
    question: "Sam is very popular. He has _____ friends.",
    answer: "A lot of",
    options: [
      "Much",
      "A few",
      "A lot of",
      "Any"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 41,
    question: "Choose the word that have the same pronunciation as the word ''wear:''",
    answer: "Where",
    options: [
      "Here",
      "Where",
      "There",
      "Were"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 42,
    question: "Add an appropriate reflexive pronoun George's mother didn't want him to take the job on the oil rig. In fact, George didn't feel very happy about it _____________. ",
    answer: "Himself",
    options: [
      "Itself",
      "Herself",
      "Himself",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 43,
    question: "Enter the word in brackets in the correct form The river_____________ (flow) very quickly today, much faster than usual.",
    answer: "Is flowing",
    options: [
      "Is flowing",
      "Was flowing",
      "Have been flowing",
      "Flew"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 44,
    question: "Call me after eight o'clock, we ____________________ dinner by then. (finish)",
    answer: "Will have finished",
    options: [
      "Finished",
      "Finishing",
      "Will have finished",
      "Ate"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 45,
    question: "Complete using can, could, or (be) able to in the correct tense. They didn't want to come with us at first, but we ___________________ persuade them.",
    answer: "Were able to",
    options: [
      "Able to",
      "Were",
      "Were able to",
      "Could"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 46,
    question: "There was so much traffic, I was lucky to get ____________ the road without being knocked over.",
    answer: "Across",
    options: [
      "Across",
      "Over",
      "Along",
      "Through"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 47,
    question: "Which of the three answers is wrong or very unlikely. She thinks _________________ living away from home when he goes to University.",
    answer: "Dan is enjoying",
    options: [
      "Dan will enjoy",
      "Dan is going to enjoy",
      "Dan is enjoying"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 48,
    question: "Choose the correct sentence that combines the following two sentences into one: A bus goes to the airport. It arrives every half hour.",
    answer: "The bus which goes to the airport arrives every half hour",
    options: [
      "The bus, that goes to the airport, arrives every half hour",
      "The bus arrives every half hour, which goes to the airport",
      "The bus which goes to the airport arrives every half hour",
      "The bus goes to the airport which arrives every half hour"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 49,
    question: "He _________ that the subject of holiday pay should be raised at the next meeting.",
    answer: "Proposed",
    options: [
      "Advised",
      "Say",
      "Proposed",
      "Make"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 50,
    question: "Is it possible to use the word ''can'' in the blank? With the factory closing next week, he ________ lose his job.",
    answer: "No",
    options: [
      "Yes",
      "No"
    ]
  },
];  